<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wolfrats</title>
    <link>https://wolfrats.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wolfrats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 11:37:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wolfrats.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Steam Controller Was Bad</title>
      <link>https://wolfrats.com/posts/controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 11:37:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfrats.com/posts/controllers/</guid>
      <description>Back in March, the wolfrats, vermin that they are, were arguing over which game controllers are worst. The general feeling was that the steam controller is bad, the game gamecube controller is pretty good, and the Playstation controllers are all right too.
Well, we decided to quantify how good we truly feel each controller is, by pitting them against each other in mortal combat. We&amp;rsquo;d each repeatedly receive a pair of controllers to compare, and could choose which was better, mark it as a tie, or skip that particular showdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MechaWolfrat Log 1</title>
      <link>https://wolfrats.com/posts/mwr_log1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 08:57:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfrats.com/posts/mwr_log1/</guid>
      <description>Wolfrat has taken to playing an irregular game of the tabletop mecha RPG Lancer. The following report details two sessions on 3/14/21 and 3/21/21.
An indescribable partnership: David Adams, a disgruntled worker with debts to pay; and Craig Boone, an ex-Union operative with a haunted conscience. Together they struck out to D15 Gateway, a station in the Long Rim on the edge of the infamous Scyllan Gap. Crushed by their bills and their pasts, they turned to bounty hunting to stay alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funorb Launchers: A story of taking off the rose-tinted glasses and crying</title>
      <link>https://wolfrats.com/posts/funorb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:03:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfrats.com/posts/funorb/</guid>
      <description>A trip through time The year is 2008. You&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last 200 hours cutting Yew logs in RuneScape to save up for a Dragon Axe, while paying $5/mo in membership fees. Then, on February 27th, from the creators of RuneScape comes a new gaming website: FunOrb. For a mere $3/mo, you get access to dozens of games, including the site&amp;rsquo;s crown jewel, Arcanists, a turn based artillery game comparable to the Worms series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alert!</title>
      <link>https://wolfrats.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 14:37:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfrats.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a test of the EWBS1. This is not a drill.
Please shelter in place before evacuating to the designated helipad. Help is on the way.
You have nothing to worry about. Your cooperation is greatly appreciated.
  The Emergency Wolfrat Broadcast System. Simulcast available in English and piglatin. Note: piglatin not yet supported. &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s About Time: Scope and Shortcomings in the Dragon Age Series</title>
      <link>https://wolfrats.com/posts/da_essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 14:37:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfrats.com/posts/da_essay/</guid>
      <description>Chunks of earth float hundreds of feet into the air, the remnants of a sacred temple and the battleground for the final fight between an evil sorcerer and the only person capable of stopping him: me, the player. Dragon Age: Inquisition, the third title in the series, concludes on a charged confrontation between Corypheus, an ancient mage who seeks to become a god, and the Inquisitor, the player character who helps build and lead an organization of (mostly) religious zealots to stop him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
